<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Browsers | The Always Yet to Be Named Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/categories/browsers/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-10T14:24:27-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nt¿]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prezto, I've Hailed an iCab]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/10/prezto-ive-hailed-an-icab/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-10T01:13:38-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/10/prezto-ive-hailed-an-icab</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve been spending less time with the hypocrites around me, and they are starting to lash out. Either there is a noticeable social withdrawal or they just don’t care for the changing me but regardless I’m feeling great.</p>

<p>I’ve gotten a new browser just so I can have 3 separate browsers with many tabs open for different tasks. Opera is for development and the live preview of this blog in its development, before it gets pushed to production (what you see now), Firefox is for casual browsing, some Facebook, some Twitter, some RSS reading. Just today I discovered my third browser, <a href="http://icab.de" title="Browser for OS X">iCab</a>.</p>

<p>iCab is apparently very strict to web standards and is overall a very speedy nice browser that I have not encountered a problem with so far. Since its based on Chromes freaky deaky engine, or whatever its called and <a href="http://www.opera.com/download/guide/?ver=12.16" title="Highly Customizable as Ever">the old version of Opera I’m purposefully using</a> is still based on the Opera engine that they were using until the recent oversimplification of their browser to a Chrome Clone (lot of those popping up lately) I have decided to use iCab for various sites that stop you and say, look, you fuck, we don’t support Opera, and even if we did, your old ass ragetty version won’t fly.</p>

<p>I also switched from <a href="https://github.com/robbyrussell/oh-my-zsh">Oh-My-ZSH</a> to <a href="http://jeromedalbert.com/migrate-from-oh-my-zsh-to-prezto/">Prezto</a> to manage my zsh shell, it’s quicker, more lightweight and I sort of a like it a little more, I hope they never ditch development and that I can tweak it some more in the next couple of days.</p>

<p>I like the way this category thing works, before I begin a post I quickly comma separate all the things on my mind and then I look back periodically when I finish with a topic to see another one up there and the words just flow. It’s quite comfy. I think I might use this outline method in less technical writings.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="images/prezto.png" title="&lsquo;Prezto in Action&rsquo;" >
<br>
<img class="center" src="images/icab.png" title="&lsquo;About iCab&rsquo;" >
<br>
<br></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
