<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Writing | The Always Yet to Be Named Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/categories/writing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-05T21:14:02-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nt¿]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Various Plugins - Facebook]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/04/testing-various-plugins-facebook/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-04T16:59:29-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/04/testing-various-plugins-facebook</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Sadly most of the better things that pop into my head end up on Facebook, a walled off garden. Although people can &ldquo;follow&rdquo; your public posts, things are mostly limited to your &ldquo;friends&rdquo;. Which is okay because most of my things have an attachment of my own personality to them and perhaps a public person which does not know me personally will take it significantly differently than a person I do personally know (Facebook &ldquo;friends&rdquo;).</p>

<p>I sort of occasionally take a swing at Twitter, but I don&rsquo;t really care for it very much. The 140 character limit feels like enslavement by some sadist who simply doesn&rsquo;t want anybody to be able to rant. Nobody comes off as angry because they are limited to 140 character and as a result, no other person reading the first persons stuff is inspired by their message to cause reform of some sort. So it&rsquo;s mostly for humor, comedians seem to do well with it.</p>

<p>I like Instagram, and the community at least seems to enjoy my contributions because I take interesting photos and play around with various Photoshop tools as well as Vingnette on Android.
There isn&rsquo;t really a lot of interaction on Instagram though, it&rsquo;s just hearts and the occasional comment (seldom anything of use). It&rsquo;s other great use is looking at pretty chicks. Man, pretty chicks are a plenty on Instagram. I think sometimes Instagram would be an interesting bare-bones dating site experiment. I noticed a while ago that Tinder got tired of people posting their Instagram links at the bottom of their Tinder profiles and built a Instagram clone right into the Tinder app.</p>

<p>So some of my better stuff is on Facebook, as such, I found a neat plugin that should allow for an embed and will proceed to try it out below and then RAKE that shit.</p>

<p><div id='fb-root'></div>
<script>(function(d, s, id) {
  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];
  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;
  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;
  js.src = '//connect.facebook.net/en_US/all.js#xfbml=1';
  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);
}(document, 'script', 'facebook-jssdk'));</script>
<div class='fb-post' data-href='<a href="https://www.facebook.com/tselkove/posts/10154755269440475">https://www.facebook.com/tselkove/posts/10154755269440475</a> &#8216;></div>
</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
