<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The Always Yet to Be Named Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-05T21:14:02-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nt¿]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Various Plugins - Facebook]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/04/testing-various-plugins-facebook/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-04T16:59:29-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/04/testing-various-plugins-facebook</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Sadly most of the better things that pop into my head end up on Facebook, a walled off garden. Although people can &ldquo;follow&rdquo; your public posts, things are mostly limited to your &ldquo;friends&rdquo;. Which is okay because most of my things have an attachment of my own personality to them and perhaps a public person which does not know me personally will take it significantly differently than a person I do personally know (Facebook &ldquo;friends&rdquo;).</p>

<p>I sort of occasionally take a swing at Twitter, but I don&rsquo;t really care for it very much. The 140 character limit feels like enslavement by some sadist who simply doesn&rsquo;t want anybody to be able to rant. Nobody comes off as angry because they are limited to 140 character and as a result, no other person reading the first persons stuff is inspired by their message to cause reform of some sort. So it&rsquo;s mostly for humor, comedians seem to do well with it.</p>

<p>I like Instagram, and the community at least seems to enjoy my contributions because I take interesting photos and play around with various Photoshop tools as well as Vingnette on Android.
There isn&rsquo;t really a lot of interaction on Instagram though, it&rsquo;s just hearts and the occasional comment (seldom anything of use). It&rsquo;s other great use is looking at pretty chicks. Man, pretty chicks are a plenty on Instagram. I think sometimes Instagram would be an interesting bare-bones dating site experiment. I noticed a while ago that Tinder got tired of people posting their Instagram links at the bottom of their Tinder profiles and built a Instagram clone right into the Tinder app.</p>

<p>So some of my better stuff is on Facebook, as such, I found a neat plugin that should allow for an embed and will proceed to try it out below and then RAKE that shit.</p>

<div id='fb-root'></div>


<script>(function(d, s, id) {
  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];
  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;
  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;
  js.src = '//connect.facebook.net/en_US/all.js#xfbml=1';
  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);
}(document, 'script', 'facebook-jssdk'));</script>


<div class='fb-post' data-href='https://www.facebook.com/tselkove/posts/10154755269440475 '></div>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failed. But Getting Back Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/03/failed-but-getting-back-up/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-03T20:31:16-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/03/failed-but-getting-back-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately due to the weirdness that is git, I have failed to move forward. I&rsquo;ve accidentally erased a number of my source files and YAML config files and as a result have had to start from scratch.</p>

<p>I will see how all this goes but until then I offer up an image for your viewing pleasure.</p>

<p><img src="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/images/dmcatolietpaper.png"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proceed With CSS]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/02/proceed-with-css/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-02T01:22:12-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/02/proceed-with-css</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I proceed with the internal development of the site. This page has been moved to slash blog, the root site at simply slash will be for honing my css development skills with my original idea.</p>

<p><img src="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/images/voila1.png" title="Scanned and Made Background Myself by Hand" alt="Now to Work on the CSS a bit"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is the Second With Pow and Rake]]></title>
    <link href="http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/01/this-is-the-second-with-pow-and-rake/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-01T03:46:19-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://chillingchakra.github.io/plate/2015/02/01/this-is-the-second-with-pow-and-rake</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It’s a sad day, here I was thinking I would go against the hipster grain that is learning Ruby and Rails and perhaps learn a counter-culture language like Perl or Haskell and then find a web framework with them but it seems Octopress has sent me into Ruby with how easy everything is to configure.</p>

<p>I shall experiment and we will have to see. I’m also going to have a look at Drupal as Linux Journal seems crazy excited about its very existence.</p>

<p>This Markdown craze isn’t something I’m crazy about either. I have to go and learn a whole new micro HTML-esque thing that lets me format my posts just the way I want.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
